[Strings]
experience_recruit_title = "Welcome, Recruit!"
experience_recruit_description = "You are now in the UNSC SPARTAN Program. If you have the guts to stick with it you just might become a Spartan. Prove yourself by earning Experience, also known as EXP, in Matchmaking Playlists."
experience_training_title = "Nice Job!"
experience_training_description = "You have performed well and have completed the requirements for Basic Training. Keep playing to earn your Spartan Insignia!"
experience_spartan_title = "Congratulations!"
experience_spartan_description = "You have proved yourself through exemplary combat and are now recognized as a member of the elite UNSC Spartan Special Forces. Display your insignia with pride, Spartan."
experience_officer_title = "Congratulations!"
experience_officer_description = "As a decorated veteran of combat you have been promoted to the UNSC Spartan Officer ranks. Make us proud, Spartan."
button_key_a_ok = " Ok"
button_key_wait = "Please wait..."