[Strings]
story0 = "<color argb=#ffffcc00>// FRAGMENT 3/7 [RECORDED VERBATIM AND INTERPRETED POST-CATACLYSM]|n|n|nD: We have the answer. We’ve built Mendicant Bias. It’s a contender class </color><color argb=#ffff3300>[AI]</color><color argb=#ffffcc00>, unlike anything we’ve ever achieved.|n|nAnd we’ve observed a pattern it|ncan exploit.</color>|n|n|n"
story1 = "<color argb=#ffffcc00>The parasite has formed a Compound Mind. When it reaches a certain mass, the Mind is able to recoil its disparate parts to create a|n</color><color argb=#ffff3300>[tactical shield]</color><color argb=#ffffcc00>. This is a simple matter of mass preservation. The thing has no compunction about|nsacrificing parts of the whole. But when the core of the Mind is threatened, it reacts violently|nand quickly. |n|nThis is the only time we ever see the thing retreat or slow its growth.</color>|n|n|n"
story2 = "<color argb=#ffffcc00>If we are to defeat it, the trick will be coordinating our forays against the </color><color argb=#ffff3300>[sprawling infection]</color><color argb=#ffffcc00> while Mendicant Bias assaults the Mind’s core. So far, we’ve been hesitant to use certain weapons because of the damage they cause surviving populations and environments. |n|nThat protocol has now been abandoned.</color>|n|n|n"
story3 = "<color argb=#ffffcc00>Mendicant will draw the Mind into battle outside the line, dealing with local biomass and other parts as best he can. The scale of the problem is vast, but the strategy|nis sound. It will require patience, materiel and an investment of energy unlike anything we have ever considered.</color>|n|n"
story4 = "<color argb=#ffffcc00>It’s a dangerous plan that carries more risk than the Array, but I believe it can work. Even if we simply force it to retreat – to retract – that will at least give us some respite. Some time to muster more resources... |n|nSome time to rescue you.</color>|n|n|n"
story5 = "<color argb=#ffffcc00>L: Are you insane\? Would you risk every life in the galaxy for this transparently futile plan\? Have you learned nothing in these last|n</color><color argb=#ffff3300>[300 years[\?]]</color><color argb=#ffffcc00>\? The thing will|nlaugh at your efforts! |n|nDo not let your concern for my welfare commit you to this suicidal scheme!|n|n// FRAGMENT ENDS</color>|n|n"
